{
    "id": "ef6c546ace2c4ed48e7b0a36bbe1744f",
    "title": "Word Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The verb form of ‘note’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "notify",
                "notification",
                "noticeable"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘black’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blacken",
                "blackish",
                "blacked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘courage’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "courageous",
                "courageously",
                "courageousness"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘ease’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easiness",
                "uneasy"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The verb form of ‘tireless’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tired",
                "tire",
                "tiresome"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘heaven’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heave",
                "heavenly",
                "hellish"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘talk’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "talking",
                "talked",
                "talkative"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The noun form of ‘stormy’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stormed",
                "storminess",
                "stormful"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The adjective form of ‘wealth’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wealthiness",
                "wealthy",
                "unwealthy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The noun form of ‘compete’ is",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "competition",
                "competed",
                "competitive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}